{ "backgroundcolor":"#000000",
 "height":103,
 "layers":[
        {
         "compression":"zlib",
         "data":"eJzt2sENwjAQRNG0Q38UwIUrlaC0gKAyhAQosjaO4x3bOzCHfyNm34EgNjymaXoomu7vRs+BnF2mWMnEkUwcycSRTBzJxJFMHMnEkUwcycSRTBzJxBFq9vNGvc5AtTULytTLVTIH0tTaZb3fDWzynIfyvDoalZxpXfc5s7Ur53l1MSo517pueW4rV43HY2rtqvV4Ta1cHg\/ChHZ5PSgTyoXwIE1O18m6psaDNm25bivnIz0tTDWuGehp2ZprNkz35DWHAPPnOiTzWr81Uvc1wNy5rlPZZ2oZg2nvd65MMo0yMdz39ppGz1ySTOPnlUmmyMk0fl6ZZIrcP5rS37nR9hBp1rypKd1HRNyvLD2pydpHzCumaK49eyP0fq+nJ7Njge5hA3i+\/di+HOpCmSI9r0GYoj1X85oiPv\/0mKI+p6419fDUumpMPT2lLs\/9dYSnxIUw9fbkXKjvwRGe0nl6nZHrF\/9nKVOsZOJIJo5k4kgmjmTiSCaOZOJIJo5k4kgmjmTiiHn2f+4JalPZFQ==",
         "encoding":"base64",
         "height":103,
         "name":"back",
         "opacity":0.5,
         "type":"tilelayer",
         "visible":true,
         "width":53,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "compression":"zlib",
         "data":"eJzt2sttwzAQRVG1k\/7cn5AmXIuX3jiAMCCH86PIF78LzCqQxANtHFLHwZB6fgax3tpp2iuaMKIJI5owogkjmjCiCSOaMKIJI5owogkjmjAamaxzfubRGUu9a\/\/u7V1TxnQaxpLlPneY5PuZYYq+r4ip98yfxlhqXZdxeU29Z\/2KiSTvEXV5TFZPlSnqspo8nkpTxGUxeT3VJq9rZIp4Zpg8Ls0U9cwyWV09U8Yz02RxtUxZz2zTyCWr8Nxh0lw903W8z7pzLL\/HkDw91zeYZKvXaxlvq9dLE007D03r10sTTTsPTevXSxNNOw9N69dbYfqP\/+fKv782WLM2r4BpZ1fLo5nkntlurqtntL+n7cPu4tI8kf1yqytShSd6rmFxzTBZPJnzp5Gr2mT1ZM8JNVelyeOpOM\/tuapMXk\/VuXvLVWGKeCq\/j5CurCnqiZg0F+p3LCOX99zkUK6983sj6dImY7qOZ10ZU+t97fz9HmI0YUQTRjRhRBNGNGFEE0Y0YUQTRjRhRBNGNGFEE0bIa\/\/m3mpBbo4=",
         "encoding":"base64",
         "height":103,
         "name":"front",
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"tilelayer",
         "visible":true,
         "width":53,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#5555ff",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "height":0,
         "name":"mods",
         "objects":[
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":759,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"outpostwall2",
                     "front":"outpostwall2"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":240,
                 "y":216
                }, 
                {
                 "height":56,
                 "id":760,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"apexshipwall"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":176,
                 "y":520
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":761,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"apexshipdetails"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":40,
                 "x":192,
                 "y":520
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":762,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"apexshipdetails",
                     "front":"apexshipdetails"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":72,
                 "x":176,
                 "y":296
                }, 
                {
                 "height":40,
                 "id":763,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"outpostsupport"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":232,
                 "y":256
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":764,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedhullpanel",
                     "front":"slopedhullpanel"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":56,
                 "x":184,
                 "y":216
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":765,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"outpostwall2",
                     "front":"outpostwall2"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":176,
                 "y":216
                }, 
                {
                 "height":16,
                 "id":766,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedhullpanel",
                     "front":"slopedhullpanel"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":72,
                 "x":176,
                 "y":304
                }, 
                {
                 "height":56,
                 "id":767,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"outpostsupport"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":232,
                 "y":520
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":768,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"apexshipdetails",
                     "front":"apexshipdetails"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":72,
                 "x":176,
                 "y":240
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":770,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"outpostwall2",
                     "front":"outpostwall2"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":240,
                 "y":600
                }, 
                {
                 "height":40,
                 "id":771,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"outpostsupport"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":184,
                 "y":256
                }, 
                {
                 "height":40,
                 "id":772,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"apexshipwall"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":176,
                 "y":256
                }, 
                {
                 "height":56,
                 "id":774,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"apexshipwall"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":240,
                 "y":520
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":777,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"outpostwall2",
                     "front":"outpostwall2"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":176,
                 "y":600
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":778,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"outpostwall2"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":72,
                 "x":176,
                 "y":248
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":779,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"apexshipdetails",
                     "front":"apexshipdetails"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":72,
                 "x":176,
                 "y":576
                }, 
                {
                 "height":40,
                 "id":780,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"apexshipwall"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":240,
                 "y":256
                }, 
                {
                 "height":48,
                 "id":782,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"glass"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":40,
                 "x":192,
                 "y":528
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":783,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedhullpanel",
                     "front":"slopedhullpanel"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":56,
                 "x":184,
                 "y":600
                }, 
                {
                 "height":56,
                 "id":785,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"outpostsupport"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":184,
                 "y":520
                }, 
                {
                 "height":16,
                 "id":786,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedhullpanel",
                     "front":"slopedhullpanel"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":72,
                 "x":176,
                 "y":224
                }, 
                {
                 "height":16,
                 "id":787,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedhullpanel",
                     "front":"slopedhullpanel"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":72,
                 "x":176,
                 "y":584
                }, 
                {
                 "height":40,
                 "id":788,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"glass"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":40,
                 "x":192,
                 "y":256
                }, 
                {
                 "height":136,
                 "id":795,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"junktech",
                     "front":"lunarbaseplatform"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":16,
                 "x":24,
                 "y":344
                }, 
                {
                 "height":136,
                 "id":796,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"slopedhullpanel"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":400,
                 "y":344
                }, 
                {
                 "height":136,
                 "id":797,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedhullpanel",
                     "front":"slopedhullpanel"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":40,
                 "y":344
                }, 
                {
                 "height":136,
                 "id":798,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedhullpanel",
                     "front":"slopedhullpanel"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":344
                }, 
                {
                 "height":136,
                 "id":799,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"slopedhullpanel"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":16,
                 "y":344
                }, 
                {
                 "height":136,
                 "id":800,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"junktech",
                     "front":"lunarbaseplatform"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":16,
                 "x":384,
                 "y":344
                }],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "width":0,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ff0000",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "height":0,
         "name":"objects",
         "objects":[
                {
                 "gid":6070,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":698,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {

                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":288,
                 "y":336
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":6070,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":699,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {

                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":128,
                 "y":336
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":6070,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":700,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {

                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":128,
                 "y":504
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":6070,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":701,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {

                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":288,
                 "y":504
                }],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "width":0,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ffff00",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "height":0,
         "name":"wiring - lights & guns",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "width":0,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ff0000",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "height":0,
         "name":"monsters & npcs",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "width":0,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#00ffff",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "height":0,
         "name":"wiring - locked door",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "width":0,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "height":0,
         "name":"outside the map",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "width":0,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "height":0,
         "name":"anchors etc",
         "objects":[
                {
                 "gid":206,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":807,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {

                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":456
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":205,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":808,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {

                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":208,
                 "y":320
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":207,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":809,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {

                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":208,
                 "y":528
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":208,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":810,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {

                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":40,
                 "y":456
                }],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "width":0,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "height":0,
         "name":"items",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "width":0,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }],
 "nextobjectid":811,
 "orientation":"orthogonal",
 "properties":
    {

    },
 "renderorder":"right-down",
 "tileheight":8,
 "tilesets":[
        {
         "firstgid":1,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/materials.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":193,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/miscellaneous.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":215,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/liquids.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":243,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/supports.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":279,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/generic.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":2166,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/ancient.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":2328,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/apex.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":2696,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/avian.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3001,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/floran.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3196,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/glitch.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3422,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/human.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3701,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/hylotl.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3932,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/novakid.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3995,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/crafting.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":4074,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/decorative.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":5479,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/door.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":5606,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/farmable.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":5681,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/furniture.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6025,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/light.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6456,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/other.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6758,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/pot.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7055,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/sapling.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7056,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/spawner.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7072,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/storage.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7303,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/teleporter.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7335,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/tools.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7340,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/trap.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7544,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/wire.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7757,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-type\/container.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":8039,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-type\/farmable.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":8117,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-type\/loungeable.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":8391,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-type\/noisy.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":8432,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-type\/teleporter.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":8457,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/railpoint.json"
        }],
 "tilewidth":8,
 "version":1,
 "width":53
}